<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HEALTH</string>
    <string name="sugar">Sugary drinks are among the most fattening items you can put into your body.This is because your brain doesn’t measure calories
        from liquid sugar the same way it does for solid food (1Trusted Source).Therefore, when you drink soda, you end up eating more total calories
        (2Trusted Source, 3Trusted Source).\n\n
        Sugary drinks are strongly associated with obesity, type 2 diabetes, heart disease, and many other health problems
        (4Trusted Source, 5Trusted Source, 6Trusted Source, 7Trusted Source). Keep in mind that certain fruit juices may be almost as bad as soda in this
        regard, as they sometimes contain just as much sugar. Their small amounts of antioxidants do not negate the sugar’s harmful effects (8Trusted Source).
    </string>
    <string name="nuts">Despite being high in fat, nuts are incredibly nutritious and healthy. They’re loaded with magnesium, vitamin E, fiber, and various
        other nutrients (9Trusted Source). Studies demonstrate that nuts can help you lose weight and may help fight type 2 diabetes and heart disease
        (10Trusted Source, 11Trusted Source, 12Trusted Source).\n\n Additionally, your body doesn’t absorb 10–15% of the calories in nuts. Some evidence also
        suggests that this food can boost metabolism (13Trusted Source). In one study, almonds were shown to increase weight loss by 62%, compared with complex
        carbs (14Trusted Source).</string>
    <string name="junkFood">The dark side of junk foods is not an unknown fact. Several research studies have shown that fast foods and processed foods have
        increased childhood obesity, heart disease and diabetes and other chronic diseases. Recently, the Delhi Government demanded a crackdown on junk food
        that is sold in schools and within 50 meters of them. Not only do they add inches to your waistline, but scientists and researchers have also
        indicated through various studies that junk food can actually cause serious damage to your brain. The worrying bit is that it’s not just years of
        poor eating, but regular consumption of junk food even for few days can lead to a mental meltdown.\n\n
        In his book, Encyclopedia of Junk Food and Fast Food, Andre F. Smith defines junk food as, "those commercial products, including candy,
        bakery goods, ice cream, salty snacks, and soft drinks, which have little or no nutritional value but do have plenty of calories, salt, and fats.
        While not all fast foods are junk foods, most are. Fast foods are ready-to-eat foods served promptly after ordering."
       The more junk food you consume, the less likely you are to consume the essential nutrients that your body relies on. You know that junk food can
        hurt your health, but you may have not known about the effects of junk food on how your brain functions</string>
    <string name="coffee">However, Meredith told MNT that the effects of caffeine can vary in each individual. This may explain the mixed outcomes of
        research on the impact of caffeine in the body. For example, he advised that individuals with anxiety disorders are more susceptible to the
        anxiety-increasing effects of caffeine. “Caffeine can also metabolize at different rates among individuals for various reasons. For example,
        cigarette smokers metabolize caffeine twice as fast as nonsmokers,” he added.\n\n
        “However, caffeine metabolism is slower among infants, pregnant women, and individuals with liver disease. In addition, some medications slow
        caffeine metabolism, which may increase the risk of caffeine intoxication. \n\n
        But the effects of caffeine also vary simply because we’re all different.” Rob M. Van Dam, adjunct associate professor of the Department of
        Nutrition at the Harvard School of Public Health, told MNT that the effects of caffeine depend on individual genetic characteristics and other
        lifestyle factors.</string>
    <string name="fatFish">Fish is a great source of high-quality protein and healthy fat.This is particularly true of fatty fish, such as salmon, which
        is loaded with omega-3 fatty acids and various other nutrients (22Trusted Source).\n\n
        Studies show that people who eat the most fish have a lower risk of several conditions, including heart disease, dementia, and depression
        (23Trusted Source, 24Trusted Source, 25).</string>

    <string name="sleep">Most adults need 7 to 8 hours of good quality sleep on a regular schedule each night. Make changes to your routine if you can not find enough time to sleep.

Getting enough sleep isn’t only about total hours of sleep. It’s also important to get good quality sleep on a regular schedule so you feel rested when you wake up.\n\n

If you often have trouble sleeping – or if you often still feel tired after sleeping – talk with your doctor.</string>

    <string name="water">Drinking enough water can have numerous benefits.

Surprisingly, it can boost the number of calories you burn.\n\n

Two studies note that it can increase metabolism by 24–30% over 1–1.5 hours. This can amount to 96 additional calories burned if you drink 8.4 cups (2 liters) of water per day (35Trusted Source, 36Trusted Source).\n\n

The optimal time to drink it is before meals. One study showed that downing 2.1 cups (500 ml) of water 30 minutes before each meal increased weight loss by 44% (37Trusted Source).</string>
    <string name="vitamin">Sunlight is a great source of vitamin D.

Yet, most people don’t get enough sun exposure.\n\n

In fact, about 41.6% of the U.S. population is deficient in this critical vitamin (42Trusted Source).

If you’re unable to get adequate sun exposure, vitamin D supplements are a good alternative.\n\n

Their benefits include improved bone health, increased strength, reduced symptoms of depression, and a lower risk of cancer. Vitamin D may also help you live longer </string>
    <string name="vegetable">Vegetables and fruits are loaded with prebiotic fiber, vitamins, minerals, and many antioxidants, some of which have potent biological effects.\n\n
        Studies show that people who eat the most vegetables and fruits live longer and have a lower risk of heart disease, type 2 diabetes, obesity, and other illnesses (50, 51).</string>
    <string name="smoke">Tobacco is a plant grown for its leaves, which are dried and fermented before being put in tobacco products.\n\nTobacco contains nicotine,
        an ingredient that can lead to addiction, which is why so many people who use tobacco find it difficult to quit.\n\nThere are also many other potentially harmful
        chemicals found in tobacco or created by burning it.</string>
    <string name="oil">Extra virgin olive oil is one of the healthiest vegetable oils.

It’s loaded with heart-healthy monounsaturated fats and powerful antioxidants that can fight inflammation (62Trusted Source, 63Trusted Source, 64Trusted Source).\n\n

Extra virgin olive oil benefits heart health, as people who consume it have a much lower risk of dying from heart attacks and strokes (65Trusted Source, 66).</string>
</resources>
